const questionArray = [
  {
  question: 'What estate did Lizzy visit while on vacation  with her aunt and uncle?',
  answers: ['Pemberly', 'Longbourn', 'Downton', 'Netherfield Park'],
  correct: 0
},
{
  question: 'What movie is a modern day Pride & Prejudice?',
  answers: [ 'You\'ve Got Mail', 'How to be Single', 'Bridget Jones\' Diary', 'Notting Hill'],
  correct: 2
},
{
question: 'Who narrowly escapes becoming an old maid by marrying Mr. Collins?',
answers: [ 'Elizabeth Bennett', 'Charlotte Lucas','Lydia Bennett', 'Anne de Bourgh'],
correct: 1
},
{
  question:'What military officer tarnishes the Bennett name by eloping with one of the sisters?',
  answers: [ 'Denny', 'Mr. Wickham', 'Mr. Darcy', 'Col. Fitzwilliam'],
  correct: 1
},
{
  question: 'According to her mother, Anne de Bourgh is destined to marry which gentleman?',
  answers: [ 'Col. Fitzwilliam', 'Mr. Collins', 'Mr. Bingley', 'Mr. Darcy'],
  correct: 3
},
{
  question: 'How many proposals does Elizabeth Bennett receive in the book?',
  answers: [3, 4, 2, 1],
  correct: 0
},
{
  question: 'What malady confines Mrs. Bennett to her room?',
  answers: [ 'Pneumonia', 'Consumption', 'Fainting', 'Nerves'],
  correct: 3
},
{
  question: 'What is Mr. Darcy\'s first name?',
  answers: ['Mark', 'Fitzwilliam', 'Charles', 'Edward'],
  correct: 1
},
{
  question: 'What are the names of the five Bennett sisters?',
  answers: ['Jane, Elizabeth, Mary, Kitty, Lydia', 'Charlotte, Elizabeth, Lydia, Georgiana, Mary', 'Caroline, Jane, Catherine, Kitty, Anne', 'Anne, Elizabeth, Mary, Rebecca, Sarah'],
  correct: 0
},
{
  question: 'A recent adaptation of Pride & Prejudice includes what unlikely character\'s?',
  answers: [ 'Vampires', 'Fairies', 'Zombies','Mr. & Mrs Claus'],
  correct: 2
}];

